<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Senior Project on Adam&#39;s Analysis</title>
    <link>https://adams-analysis.netlify.app/categories/senior-project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Senior Project on Adam&#39;s Analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://adams-analysis.netlify.app/categories/senior-project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Through Researching</title>
      <link>https://adams-analysis.netlify.app/2022/07/19/through-researching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adams-analysis.netlify.app/2022/07/19/through-researching/</guid>
      <description>PlanningWhen getting started with a new project, researching your question and what other people have done is helpful in the beginning stages. There is a balance that needs to be found, however. Doing enough research that you know roughly what to expect but not so much that you never start. Maybe I struck that balance for a beginner. Often, you find better solutions or better questions to issues that you may have while working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I&#39;ve Learned Working With Facebook&#39;s API</title>
      <link>https://adams-analysis.netlify.app/2022/07/18/what-i-ve-learned-working-with-facebook-s-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adams-analysis.netlify.app/2022/07/18/what-i-ve-learned-working-with-facebook-s-api/</guid>
      <description>The SituationAs part of my analysis for my mom’s bakery, one of the questions that my mom has asked is how does social media affect revenue and number of transactions. To answer her question, I have been learning to pull data from Facebook’s API. I have learned so much! Here are some of the things that I wish I knew when I first started.
Facebook’s API StructureFacebook’s API is set up in a graph structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior Project Inspiration</title>
      <link>https://adams-analysis.netlify.app/2022/05/25/senior-project-inspiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adams-analysis.netlify.app/2022/05/25/senior-project-inspiration/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionMy dad is a wise man. Ever since I switched my degree from accounting to data science in the summer of 2020, he has put the bug in my ear to make some kind of program that can predict how many cinnamon rolls that one of my mom’s bakeries should make. I’ve thought that this is a great idea! However, I have not really known how to execute on this idea until a few months ago.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
